{
    "id": "ff3adfa7c25b4b4fb12208bf77eb5e2c",
    "title": "Simple Present Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "When .................................... you get up in the morning?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fa582a36fc80468d834991412920ae2b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ............................................ up at six o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "gets"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e34fc9134034647b4f79f7efb356461"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .............................................. breakfast at 9 am.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2a5ae5158fcc4daaa6544daa78c8f2c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................................. science at a private school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "teach",
                "teaches"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9d825cd4df746bb8f0bc9ba1c765cf1"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane ............................................ up at five o’clock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "gets"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6471c7f3c6b9436ea8dc7444db6ef2b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Vicky ............................................. at a bank.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "works"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a0a47ee0448e44b59a372a13bac5bc16"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ........................................... a six figure salary.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "earn",
                "earns"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1f2ad73401d24ba894ea700077c3463f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .......................................... a beauty parlor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "run",
                "runs"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5e7b0d9a314642559da8b8ca2141f40d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You .............................................. well",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sing",
                "sings"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8bc2003a3c97407a837abb6fdbd544b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ............................................. at bank.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "work",
                "works"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9a807ce9d2a40eab5b41df1d73a3656"
        }
    ]
}